&gt；&gt；Kyle：我多年来一直使用的一个隐喻，它对我很有效
&gt;&gt; Kyle: One metaphor that I have used for years that works well for me and
也许会对你有好处。
maybe will work well for you.
作用域相互嵌套的概念类似于建筑物
This idea of scopes being nested within each other is similar to a building
里面有个又大又高的电梯，好吗？
with a big tall elevator in it, okay?
想象一下，如果你走进一栋大楼，你正在寻找什么，但是
Imagine if you went into a building and you were looking for something but
你不知道它在哪里。
you didn't know where it was.
你只是知道它在大楼里的某个地方或者
You just knew it was somewhere in the building or
可能在大楼的某个地方。
probably somewhere in the building.
你应该从一楼开始。
You'd start on the first floor.
你只需要做一个基本的线性搜索。
You just do basically a linear search.
从一楼开始，在那里找。
Start on the first floor, look for it there.
如果你找不到，就乘电梯到下一层，
And if you don't find it, take the elevator to the next floor,
在那里找找。
look for it there.
如果你找不到，那就一遍又一遍地做。
If you don't find it, do that again and again and again.
最终你会到达大楼的顶层。
And eventually you're gonna arrive at the top floor of the building.
你要么找到它，要么找不到，但没有别的地方可去。
And you either find it or you don't, but there's nowhere else to go.
所以从概念上讲，一楼是我们目前的范围，
So conceptually the first floor is our current scope where the reference is,
顶层是全球范围。
and the top floor is the global scope.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我们稍后会在课程中回到这个比喻。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: We'll come back to this metaphor a later time in the course.
所以如果这对你有用的话就把它留在你的脑子里，
So just kinda keep that in your head if that works for you,
一次爬一层楼的想法。
this idea of going one floor up at a time.
我们不会立即跳到全球范围，我们只是一次走一层楼。
We don't immediately jump to the global scope, we just go one floor at a time.